The Child of Visayas...
Attorney Benjamin Santos!
Ben, it's me! Let me in!
- Ma'am--
- Ben!
- Stop!
Your sister?
You hid that from me for eight years!
What am I supposed to do with that?
I didn't lie. I just didn't say.
- No! No!
- What do you want?
They say that I'm crazy.
That my screws are loose.
- She could end up killing you.
- Ma!
If that time comes,
it's better to have a gun than a knife.
I just really need to speak with her.
I have something important to tell her.
Ben killed my husband.
Did you see it?
No. But I know he did it.
You'll love this.
I know something about you.
No, don't.
I remember every single story
Gingging told me.
- Don't! Don't say it!
- About how you killed your father.
- Ten million. So we can start over.
- Right, Regina?
- Regina, please.
Ten million.
Ben?
Ben...
Ben!
Where is she?
- Who was that?
- The woman at the gate?
- I don't know. I don't know.
- Who was that?
- I almost ran over her.
- What?
Who was that, Nanny?
What did she look like?
She had fair skin.
A pretty face, petite body.
She said she had
something important to tell you.
Who was that?
- She didn't give her name?
- No, sir.
I don't know. Maybe she's Beth's friend.
She must've sent her here.
I don't know.
Do not let anyone in.
- Make sure of it.
- That's right.
- Good thing she left.
- Stay alert.
Did she say anything to you, Nanny?
Ging?
Did you drink your medicine?
That looks great.
I didn't catch the balloon.
It slipped out of my hand.
So it flew away.
It's free now.
It isn't free...
it's alone.
There's a difference.
Ging?
Get better soon, okay?
So you can live with us.
We can live happily with Ana.
Why should I believe you?
You never tell the truth.
You're a big liar.
I know you don't love me.
Thanks.
Mm.
Ging.
I love you.
I love you so much.
What makes you think I don't?
Hmm?
Then why are you sending me away
to a facility?
And you tie me up.
You keep me locked away and hidden.
Ging, you're sick, remember?
This is what's best for you.
How is this supposed to be
what's best for me?
Where are you?
Huh?
You're in this fancy house.
Living a good life
with your beautiful wife.
And what about me?
Mara's the one
who takes care of me, not you.
I love you, Ging.
Mara's here because of me.
I pay her to take care of you.
You should be taking care of me.
Ging.
Ging, you ran away, remember?
I had to work hard
and build a life for myself.
So when we'd meet again--
You could send me to a mental facility?
Ging...
Ging.
I just want you to get better.
Nobody loves me.
They've all left me.
Ging.
You've all left me!
Ging. I'm still here.
I love you.
I am your brother.
Yes, you're my brother.
So you have no choice but to love me.
If I wasn't your sister,
you would've killed me a long time ago.
You only love one person.
You only love yourself.
A compound? What's inside it?
I don't know.
The woman at the store doesn't know
what's inside either.
I just saw a guy with a gun.
Are you sure, Bridge?
What if Angel's not there?
I showed the woman
Angel's picture. She said...
Oh, yes. The girl with the fair skin!
She sent money from here.
If I'm not mistaken,
she lives in the Abismo Compound.
She said the girl had fair skin!
Angel has fair skin. It has to be her!
What if we report it to the police?
Remember? Rona said
no one reports the cops.
But we need help.
Who knows what happened to Angel.
It's nice to walk around here.
Thank you for joining me.
A change of scenery will do you good.
Do you like your dress?
Okay.
After the fundraiser
and my friend's wedding,
I'll make you another one.
It really suits you.
What is a fundraiser?
It's like a... party.
They'll showcase my designs,
and people will come to buy them.
The money we'll raise will be donated
to a charitable organization.
Like a hospital or orphanage.
You're going to give your clothes away
for free?
Mm-hmm. To help the poor.
You're such a good person.
You care for those in need.
Like me.
My brother and I
used to rely on food drives.
Did you know that?
Yes.
You know, he's really nice.
He'd always protect me from bullies.
There used to be bad kids
in our neighborhood.
And also from...
Papa.
He'd always protect me from Papa.
One time, when Papa touched me,
he said, "Stop!
No! Don't do that to Ging!"
How would he touch you?
Like this.
Right here.
Sometimes...
I don't know. I don't remember.
I'd just feel bad for Ben.
He'd always get beaten up.
But he's a nice kid.
He's nice to me too, Regina.
He helps a lot of people in Vallente.
He's loved by many.
Sure. He's a nice guy.
But he's done terrible things too.
What do you mean?
Have I told you
it's not just Joel he'd killed?
He killed Papa too.
I saw it with my own eyes.
That's not a good joke, Regina.
Do I look like I'm joking?
Do you really think
you know everything about him?
He didn't even go to school.
He's not a real lawyer.
He's such a fraud.
Ben isn't a real lawyer?
I really like this dress.
It suits my necklace.
Joel gave this to me.
Yes, it's pretty.
Come on, Regina. Let's go home.
Joel?
- Joel!
- Regina!
Joel!
Regina.
You're not him.
- Let's go.
- It's not him.
Come on.
I know, I know!
Let's not argue about this.
You shouldn't have let her out.
I thought it would be okay, Ben.
We had security with us.
Anyway, I'm on my way home. Okay?
We've also reported it to the police,
but they told us
we didn't have enough evidence
to make a case.
What did you expect?
Eric has connections
within the police force.
But wait, did you go alone?
That's too dangerous.
I need to know the truth.
My God, Bridgette.
I can't do that kind of thing.
It's not that.
But do you know someone
who can help us get Angel
out of that goddamn compound?
Here. Call that number.
Who is this? How can they help me?
Just call them and say you know me.
Oh, whoever that is,
I really hope they can help Angel.
Excuse me, one gin tonic, please.
Ow! Watch it.
Sorry, sorry.
Isn't that the physical therapist?
The one who worked for the Saguils?
You mean, the girl who tried
stealing Ana Santos's husband?
Yeah.
Are you guys talking about me?
Yeah, we'd like to know how you do it.
First, be a skank.
Then, pretend to be a PT
to get close to married men.
What did you say?
- You've got a lot of nerve.
- Hey!
- What did you do?
- Leave me alone, you two.
Oh, did I offend you?
- You've got some guts, don't you?
- Ow! Let me go! Ow!
You deserve it, whore!
- Take this!
- Stop! Hey!
- Take that!
- Stop!
You think you're tough, huh?
- You're just a skank!
- You deserve that!
If I were you, I'd leave this place!
Get out, skank!
Stop!
Hello?
You finally remembered to call!
I was wondering how you've been.
Betchay?
What happened to you?
At the bar...
I got...
I got beaten up.
You got into a fight?
You can't just get wasted.
You're an outsider!
Diane, what did I do wrong?
Why is this so hard for me?
All I did was love a guy.
You loved a married man.
But...
that's how love is, right?
You can't help it.
You just feel it.
You just... love.
Betchay, the real question is...
are you sure that's love?
I wouldn't be crazy over Ben like this...
if it wasn't love.
Why?
Do you think love is the only thing
that could drive a person mad?
What... what do you mean?
Sometimes, loneliness is far worse.
Being alone...
takes a lot out of you.
So, if you ask me again, Beth,
if we can choose the people we love...
yes, we can.
You can choose.
And you can choose the people
who actually love you back.
Your family.
Yourself.
Come home, Beth, please?
We will all be waiting for you here.
He didn't even go to school.
He's not a real lawyer.
Hey.
Oh. Hey, stranger.
How are you?
Good.
No!
- I don't want to go, Ben!
- It's safe there.
- People are nice.
- What's going on?
What's happening? Wait!
Let her go!
- I don't want to go!
- Let her go! Let her go!
- Stop hurting her!
- I don't want to go!
Ben, she's your sister!
You shouldn't do this to her!
- I know that, Ana.
- She doesn't wanna go!
But she's unstable.
She's unstable. She has to go.
She has to go. Trust me, please.
Trust me, I know what I'm doing.
- Ging...
- No, please, Ben!
I'll come back for you, okay?
We're going to fix this.
It won't take long.
Everyone there is nice.
I promise, I won't leave you alone.
- I don't want to!
- I won't leave you alone.
Ana, I don't want to go.
I don't want to!
Ben, I don't want to go!
I really don't want to!
- Don't make me go!
- I won't leave you alone.
Please...
I don't want to go there!
Don't make them take me, please.
I don't want to go!
I don't want to go there!
Please, Ben.
I'll come back for you.
I promise, I'll come back for you.
Okay?
Wait for me, okay? Just be good.
Go on now.
Come on now. It's for your own good.
You'll be fine over there.
I got this. Thank you.
You did the right thing.
I should know.
I also get treated for my mental health.
That's all you want for your sister.
I don't know,
but why do I feel like...
Ana doesn't like what I did?
Not everything is right feels right.
And not everything that feels wrong
is wrong.
Maybe Ana is concerned about your sister
because she reminds her of her brother.
She wants to help Regina because...
she couldn't help her brother before.
Just try to understand.
She's been through so much.
Actually...
there's one more thing
I wanted to discuss with you,
if that's okay.
The Bais house.
I'd like to buy the Bais house.
Of course,
at the price that you like.
It's a gift for my wife.
Of course.
If that's what you want.
I'm sure Ana would love that too.
That's all I want.
You know, Ben...
sometimes I wonder.
What would happen to my daughter
without you?
He's a nice guy.
But he's done terrible things too.
Do you really think
you know everything about him?
He's not a real lawyer.
He's such a fraud.
Have I told you
it's not just Joel he'd killed?
He killed Papa too.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Ana! Ana!
Ana!
What are you doing here?
I'm ready to tell the whole truth.
Not here.
I asked you before,
and you said you didn't know Ben.
But now you're telling me
you know something about him.
Why should I believe you?
I only said that because I promised Ben.
But I'm not his mistress.
I'm his sister's nurse.
And the house you went to...
that's where your husband was hiding us.
Ben said that was the first time
he saw his sister again.
That's not true.
He's hiding a lot from you.
Like this.
Look at it.
This is one of the copies
that slipped past Ben
and Attorney De Castro.
Check this.
Yes, Benjamin Santos is a common name.
But if he really graduated there,
then there should be two of them
in the yearbook.
No, no.
I called the university,
and they said Ben did graduate there.
Maybe he just didn't sign up for this.
This is the IBP number
that he's been using.
This is the one. Right?
I traced the registered owner.
It turned out to be a different Ben.
It's the one, right?
Attorney Ben's IBP number?
Indeed, this IBP number is registered
to Attorney Benjamin Santos.
But why are you searching for him?
He has long been deceased.
W-What?
For almost ten years now.
He's been dead for years.
Ben is a good person. He's a good man.
- He's good...
- He's good at lying!
You married a fraud, Ana!
Who told you about this?
Regina?
You know she's sick, right?
I came face-to-face
with someone from Ben's past.
My father worked at your law firm
for many years.
And still, I never received any help.
What... would you like to know?
I just want to know if you can help me.
Of course.
Sure. I'll help you.
If it's what will cause Ben's downfall.
That bastard Ben...
he hogged all the luck in the world.
While the rest of us are struggling,
still-- still sunken deep here
at the bottom.
Who killed my father?
Was it Ben?
It wasn't Ben.
It was De Castro.
De Castro killed your father.
De Castro fought with another lawyer
from a different firm.
De Castro shot him.
How very unfortunate...
that your father witnessed it all.
They killed my father...
to shut him up?
It was Ben who made it seem like
your father was a drug addict
and committed suicide.
He was the one who covered up everything
to avoid anything from coming out.
When I found out the truth...
I was so infuriated
that I wanted to take revenge.
I want justice for my father.
Sue De Castro.
Ask for Brian's help
if he's really the one
who knows everything.
Brian is gone, Ana.
After that day,
I never saw him again.
He's gone.
No, I just saw Brian.
He stopped by our house.
- He's going through something.
- No, he's not.
Ben's money is all he's after.
Ana, with how long
I've been looking after Regina,
she's told me a lot about the things
Ben does to other people.
About what he did to Joel.
To their father.
You believe her?
Even if Regina has
an intellectual disability, in here...
in here, she's genuine.
It's too late to do anything
about my father's case now.
But you...
you can still save yourself.
- Good morning.
- Good morning, sir.
Why is there
just one set? Did Ana eat already?
She already left, sir.
Huh?
Isn't today Ma'am Katrina's wedding day?
She even brought her dress with her.
She might have gone there already.
She didn't mention anything to me
about that.
I was taken by surprise as well.
But it's Ma'am Katrina's wedding,
so I didn't think too much of it.
Shit.
You don't have to pick me up.
I'll take a taxi
when I get to the airport.
You're bringing all of that?
Aren't you going back there?
Beth, tell us what's wrong.
Nothing. I just really wanted to go home.
Just last time,
we're talking about
how lucky you are in Vallente.
Right? Now, all of a sudden,
you're coming home.
Because of you.
You two are the reason I want to go home.
Really?
You keep thinking of weird things.
I miss you.
That's why I'm going home. That's it.
Okay. If that's the case,
then bring us lots of souvenirs.
Bring home some sweet food too.
Those are yummy!
And when you get here, let's eat out!
- Sure!
- My favorite place!
You keep thinking of food!
It's all just food with you!
- 'Cause I'm hungry--
- Beth, I like seafood.
Mine's seafood, okay?
I want lots of crabs!
- Okay. See you, Beth!
- See you, Beth!
- Take care, okay?
- Take care.
Get away from me, you lunatic!
Nurse,
she's having an episode!
Don't bother me!
- I'll do whatever I want!
- Nurse Chloe,
- you have to ask for help.
- She's so nosy.
She's so nosy!
Ben.
Fuck you, Mara.
I know everything, Ben.
You bastards.
Even though De Castro killed my dad,
you're the reason why there's still
no justice for his death!
That's why I'll ruin both of your lives.
I just started with you.
Well, I can't blame you for being stupid.
You knew.
Obviously.
You think I didn't know?
If you didn't want anything,
would you put up with my sister?
Well, life is like that.
We're all just using each other.
I just targeted Regina
because I needed to know
what really happened to my father.
But I felt nothing for her but sympathy.
I genuinely treated her
like my real family,
which she never felt from you.
Damn you.
Your sympathies are fake, Mara.
You brainwashed my sister
so that she'd be angry with me.
Right?
- Right?
- Say whatever you want to say, Ben.
Because the life you know ends here.
The life you built.
You should be the one tied and locked up.
Regina isn't the crazy one here.
It's you.
Mara, don't ever come near--
Hey, have you heard?
Did you know
someone escaped again a while ago?
Really? Who is it this time?
It's patient Santos.
And she just got here.
Ow!
Sorry.
Ana.
You are extra spaced out today.
Are you sure you're marrying Carlos?
What?
On the day of my wedding...
you're going to say that, really?
It just crossed my mind.
I know Carlos and I
have been together for a long time.
I even did a loyalty test on him...
and he passed.
So...
If you don't want to do it, don't do it.
Because once you commit...
everything will change.
Even the parts of you
that you're trying to protect.
Ana, you're scaring me.
That's the thing with marriages.
Some yeses follow you
for the rest of your life.
So are you going to do this or not?
I'll do this.
I think Carlos is worth taking the risk.
Like Ben, right?
Good for you.
You're all set.
I'm just gonna go get changed.
- Hello?
- Sir, Regina escaped.
What?
Yes. She got out of the facility.
Sir, did you happen to see this woman?
She's wearing a patient's uniform.
I'm sorry. I haven't seen her.
Thank you.
Miss!
Hello, did you happen to see this woman?
She's wearing a patient's uniform.
Maybe she passed by here.
- Sorry, but we haven't seen her.
- Thanks.
- Ma'am, please stop!
- Don't touch me!
- You'll get in trouble, ma'am!
- Ma'am, that's enough.
What are you all looking at?
Stop staring at me!
Ma'am, that's enough.
Don't come near me,
or else I'll throw this at you!
I was just looking around!
Uh, mister?
You can drop me off here.
Security!
Can I leave this with you for a moment?
- Sure, ma'am.
- Thank you.
I'll come back for it, I promise.
There's a crazy person inside!
- Don't touch me!
- She's throwing a tantrum.
- Stay away from me!
- What's going on?
There's a crazy person inside.
Don't touch me! Let me go!
- Regina!
- Ma'am, that's enough.
- Stay away from me!
- Regina!
- Ma'am.
- Thank God I found you. I'm here.
You're a monster! You're a monster!
You're a monster!
- Regina, it's--
- Monster!
A monster!
- There's a monster! A monster!
- Regina!
Regina! Wait!
Okay. Thank you.
Please call me right away
if she comes back.
Thank you.
Ging.
- Regina!
- Leave me alone!
- Wait!
- Go away!
Regina! Please, wait!
No! Go away!
- Regina, stop!
- Stay away from me!
- It's just me!
- Listen to me!
- Stay away from me!
- Please, listen to me!
Ging...
I don't want to!
Mara!
Fuck!
Mara? Mara?
Mara! Mara!
This can't be happening!
Mara!
No, Mara!
This can't be happening!
Mara!
This is all my fault...
Ben, this is all my fault!
This is all my fault!
Why does it matter
what you think is real or not, Ana?
Are you a client?
I am his wife.
There is something
you need to know about Ben.
We will conduct
a wide-scale search at sea.
Sir, there are a lot of secrets here.
What about this yacht, what's its secret?
Spotless, right? Only Attorney Ben
keeps his yacht this clean.
We can't get in touch with Beth.
Her flight wasn't canceled.
Sir, another body was recovered.
I wonder
how many bodies were dumped out here?
We're worried about Beth.
We couldn't get a hold of her.
Is this about me?
It's always about you, love.
Everything...
is about you.